I welcome you to our live stream too!
Hello!
I'm Yuna Hase.
I'm Miyu Fujita.
Hello.
I'm shooting the video without
permission.
I'm so happy.
The reason why I'm shooting the video
is that
Karen is going to the aquarium
because she has a practice of dolphin
show.
We also wanted to go with her.
We wanted to go with her.
Because we are doing our best.
We wanted to support her.
If we ask her to do that, adults will
say no.
They will say,
You are terrible.
She is following us without permission.
We are following him and the staffs so
that he won't find out.
We want to enjoy the day.
If we wear our uniforms, he will find
out.
We are safe.
Yeah!
Thank you for watching!
We are going to change our clothes and
go to the aquarium.
We are going to see how far we can go
without being noticed.
We are going to take the same train as
Karen.
Karen has arrived.
I'm here.
Can you see me?
I'm wearing headphones.
I'm not noticed.
I'm walking around.
I'm lost.
He's coming up.
Is this a prank?
Is it a convenience store?
He ran away because he thought I was
coming up.
But, it was a convenience store.
I wonder what he will buy.
Maybe a pumpkin and a puffer fish?
I think so.
The point of this video is that if he
or the staff finds out, they will be
angry.
They will ask me what I'm doing.
So,
I'm scared.
I'll do my best.
The staff is here.
Please subscribe to this channel.
We are going to the fair.
I didn't notice it.
I'm watching the fair.
It looks delicious.
Are you going to buy something?
She is gone.
I like the fair.
I'm looking at everything.
Kansai Fair.
Before going to the aquarium, we should
go to the fair.
We are going to ride a bicycle.
We should ride a bicycle to avoid being
seen.
We should hurry up.
We are going to hurry up.
Please subscribe to this channel.
We are in the train.
We are going to get on the train.
It's amazing to practice dolphin every
time we get on the train.
Our leader is amazing.
Karen is not good at swimming, but she
overcomes it and swims with dolphins.
After that, we have a lesson.
After that, we have a showroom.
Karen is doing various things in front
of the showroom.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Let's go!
I want to get closer to him.
I have 20 minutes.
I like this thrill.
The color of the hair is changing.
It's true.
It's blond.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I'm going to the train station.
I'm going to the train station of
Karen.
I'm sleeping.
Thank you for watching.
I'm waiting for the train.
I'm getting on the train.
I'll get on it once.
I'm too excited.
I'll get off the train and wait for the
train.
I'll wait for the train.
I'd love to hear what you think!
I'm going to the next place.
I'm so scared.
I just got here.
I'm here.
I'm not used to this.
I did it.
Please subscribe to my channel.
We arrived at the scene.
I'm so tired.
We're going to the bus station.
It's like a police station.
How long are we going to carry our
bags?
He got on the bus.
We're going to catch up with him by
taxi.
The bus has started.
Let's chase that bus.
Which one?
This bus.
Oh, no. We have to hurry.
How many years have you been a driver?
Yes.
Wow.
It's long.
It's amazing.
Have you ever been a celebrity?
I haven't.
Hold on
She's coming!
I can see them!
In such a dangerous situation
Is she trying to catch something with
the coffee machine
Maybe she's coming from the back gate
This somewhat looks like a plan
Three River Island
Yay!
We're here! Yay!
I wonder how much the admission fee is.
We can go there as students, right?
That's right.
We didn't have to go to the aquarium.
And we didn't have to talk to the
staff.
That's right.
Let's go to the aquarium!
Yay!
I'm looking forward to it!
Let's take a commemorative photo.
This is a picture of a student on a
school trip.
We took a commemorative photo.
Yay!
Please subscribe to my channel!
I'm
However, Misadami ZUNI was able to go
back to her home without being noticed
by the ISAKUZes.
I was caught by the staff after
arriving at the aquarium.
I was caught.
I was having fun in front of the
aquarium.
I was caught.
The staff is amazing.
They are watching us.
I'm sorry.
We came here without hesitation.
We asked them to help us.
The staff was on duty.
It's cute.
We will enjoy the aquarium with the
general public.
We will watch the aquarium of Karen.
We will watch it.
We will enjoy it.
We have to be caught by Karen.
The staff is on duty.
We are on duty.
We are a team.
We will look around the aquarium.
We will enjoy the aquarium.
I will go.
Wow.
I can swim in this.
That's great.
Miu, you can feed them here.
You can be their friend.
I feel like I'm introducing myself.
Wow!
No, no, no.
I'm not saying wow.
I'm introducing myself.
I'm Missing No.1, I'm Toku-san.
Nice to meet you.
Wow!
She's waving at us.
We've arrived at the second floor.
This is the world's largest sea
monster.
Is there a sea monster?
There are so many.
There it is!
Look!
Karen is here.
She is practicing.
She is listening to the explanation.
I participated the story of the sea
monster.
I'll definitely do my best.
I brought a baby doll today.
It's a baby white dog.
I didn't know that there was a baby
white dog.
I brought a baby white dog.
Thank you for watching.
I think it's dangerous.
Let's go to the front.
I got a finger prick.
It's dangerous.
There is a big wheel.
I got a finger prick.
Good luck, good luck, Karen!
She doesn't notice it.
She doesn't notice it at all, so I'll
try to do something strange.
She's saying good luck.
Oh, she got it!
Are you concentrating?
Look at this!
They are crawling.
I think I can reach the goal if I get
close to the goal.
I can see the goal.
Good luck!
I'm going to do it.
I'm going to be found out.
Don't look at me.
She's thinking about it.
Wait a minute.
I don't think anyone knows.
That's true.
It's a completely different position.
That's amazing.
She's serious.
Our leader is amazing.
She is doing her best.
I'm going to see the sea queen next.
She is a member of the aquarium.
I'll make her think that I'm a member
of the aquarium.
And I'll walk in front of her.
I'll do my best.
Hello.
I'm going to say hello to her during
the break.
I'm going to say hello to her.
I'll do my best.
I'm practicing without a break.
I asked her if I didn't need to drink
water.
She said, I'm drinking water.
Another green tea?
We are working hard to make a video.
We are hiding and waiting for the sun
to rise.
We'll do our best.
Good bye.
Thank you for watching.
I'm awake.
I see.
Thank you for watching.
Ouch! Ouch!
Next!
Hang on a moment.
Nagoya civil training center
I'm sorry.
No, no.
You don't have to look like that.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
You look more and more like that.
You don't have to look so serious.
Why are you all doing this?
What are you doing?
What is that?
How many times do I have to do this?
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm scared.
What is this?
Thank you for your hard work.
What are you doing?
Hello.
I'm...
Actually, I just got back from the
place where we met at Sendai station.
I'm so happy.
Please subscribe to this channel.
I saw her sleeping while wearing
headphones on the train.
Where did you see me?
In front of you.
I saw you sitting opposite the driver
in the bus.
I saw you sneaking in your bag and
doing something.
I saw you swimming with dolphins.
I was swimming a lot.
Do your best.
I think you will finish the show when
this video is uploaded.
I'm doing the show and then I'm doing
the dance lesson.
It was my routine.
You are amazing.
That's why it says shooting.
It doesn't say what you are doing.
It's a shooting for two people.
Good job.
That's all for today.
Thank you.